Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series V. Housing
  - Housing- General - 1920s-1930s (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - The Fibre of the Nation (Box 7, Folder 15)
      W.H. Schuchardt, Milwaukee Housing Commission member, Rough Draft w/ handwritten notes, for "The American Architect"
    - Housing Under Capitalism, January 1, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Sidney Hill, International Pamphlets No. 46
    - Federal Participation In Large-Scale Housing Since 1932, May 1, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Map, National Association of Housing Officials
    - Housing - Public and/or Private, January 1, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Edith Elmer Wood, Survey Graphic, vol. 24, no. 1
    - Housing Digest., November 1, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Public Works Administration, Housing Division, Research and Information Branch, November 1935, No. 1
    - Housing Digest., January 1, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Public Works Administration, Housing Division, Research and Information Branch, January 1936, No. 2
    - Housing Digest., April 1, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Public Works Administration, Housing Division, Research and Information Branch, April 1936, No. 3
    - The Housing Problem - How Planned Distribution May Prevent Crowding, January 1, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Sir Raymond Unwin, Journal of The Royal Sanitary Institute, vol. 56, no. 10
    - Recent Progress In Workmen's Housing In the Americas (Box 7, Folder 15)
      The Pan American Union.
    - Can America Build Houses?, January 1, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Miles L. Colean, Public Affairs Pamphlets, No. 19 (updated version in 7-16)
    - Better Housing, Better Health (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Federal Works Agency, U.S. Housing Authority
    - The Businessman and Public Housing (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Labor and Housing (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Tax Exemption of Public Housing (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Rehousing Relief Families (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Low Rents for Low Incomes (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Housing- General - 1940s (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - A Housing Program... For Now and Later, February 1, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      National Public Housing Conference
    - Can America Build Houses?, January 1, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Miles L. Colean, Public Affairs Pamphlets, No. 19 (2 copies)
    - Postwar Planning for the Construction Industry, June 23, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      The Producers' Council, Inc.
    - Factors Essential to a Post-War Housing Program, November 6, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Dorothy Roseman, National Committee on Housing, Inc.
    - The Association's Statement to the Lanham Committee, February 18, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      National Association of Housing Officials Bulletin, No. 160,
    - The Post War Construction Market, June 23, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      S. Morris Livingston, U.S. Department of Commerce, Talk Before the Producers Council
    - The Post War Housing Challenge, December 4, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      John B. Blandford, Jr., National Housing Agency
    - Conference on Land Planning and Community Protection In the Emergency Housing Program, May 23, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Public Administration Clearing House
    - Housing Needs. A Preliminary Estimate., November 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      National Housing Agency
    - Housing After World War I. Will History Repeat Itself?, December 1, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Housing for the United States After the War, May 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Notes on Emerging Postwar Housing Policies In Certain Other Countries, July 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - The Housing Situation. The Factual Background, June 1, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Housing and Home Finance Agency
  - Housing- General - 1940s (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Health and the Modern City, May 1, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      CIBA Symposia, Vol. 9, No. 12
    - Housing and Urban Planning, April 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      The American Institute of Architects
    - Urban Housing and Crowding. Relocation to Certain Population Characteristics as Indicated By National Health Survey Data, January 1, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Public Health Bulletin, No. 261. Federal Security Agency, U.S. Public Health Service
    - A Housing Program for America (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Charles Abrams, League for Industrial Democracy
    - FHA Home Owner's Guide (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Federal Housing Administration
    - Garden Space In Relation to Housing, June 1, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Institute of Landscape Architects
    - Statement of Housing Policy and Program, July 15, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      National Association of Housing Officials, Bulletin 157
    - Economics of Housing. A Study Outline., May 1, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Bertram M. Gross, U.S. Department of Agriculture
    - City-Planning Housing. The First Line of Advance, April 1, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Hugo Leipziger
    - Comparative Analysis of the Principal Provisions of State Housing Authority Laws Relating to Housing, Slum Clearance, and Urban Redevelopment, February 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - A Descriptive Analysis of the Basic Permanent Housing Functions Being Administered by Its Three Constituent Units Under the General Direction and Supervision of its Administrator, July 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - What Does the Housing Program Cost?, March 1, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      U.S. Housing Authority
    - Progress of Public Housing in the United States, August 1, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Margaret H. Schoenfeld, U.S. Department of Labor, Monthly Labor Review,
    - Housing In the United States. Problems and Policy., July 1, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Catherine Bauer, International Labour Review, vol. 52, no. 1
    - A New Look at Housing, February 25, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Mrs. Samuel I. Roseman, National Committee on Housing, Inc.
    - A Survey of Housing Authorities in Thirty-Three Cities, July 1, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Bureau of Municipal Research, University of Oregon
  - Housing- General - 1940s (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Good Shelter for Everyone, October 28, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Department of Research and Education,
    - Official List of Local Housing Authorities. Total As of August 15, 1941 -- 629, August 15, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Housing Facts., January 1, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Improvement of Housing In Cities, April 29, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      U.S. Chamber of Commerce
    - Public Housing. Yesterday, Today, Tomorrow., May 20, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Herbert Emmerich, Federal Public Housing Authority.
    - How Big Is the Housing Job?, September 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Housing America., January 1, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Ric-wiL Company (Manufacturers of Insulated Pipe Conduit Systems)
    - Scoring Community Desireability, February 9, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Housing Authority of the County of Cook, Illinois
    - Public Housing Dividends., September 1, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Survey Mid-Monthly, Federal Public Housing Authority
    - Public Housers Answer Industry's Questions, October 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Howard L. Holtzendorff
    - Community Services and Public Housing., November 1, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - A Private Realtor's View of Public Housing, May 23, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Roland R. Randall, Citizens' Housing Council of New York
    - Map of Public Housing Projects, October 22, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Supplement to Public Housing
    - Public Housing., July 2, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Weekly Publication, Federal Works Agency and the U.S. Housing Authority, vol. 2, no.1 through vol. 2, no. 13
    - Public Housing. For the Planners and Builders of American Communities, October 2, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Publication, Federal Works Agency and the U.S. Housing Authority, vol. 2, no. 32, vol. 2, no. 14 - vol. 2, no. 32
    - Public Housing. For the Planners and Builders of American Communities, March 15, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Publication, Federal Works Agency and the U.S. Housing Authority, vol. 2, no. 32, vol. 2, no. 33 - vol. 2, no. 33
    - Public Housing. For the Planners and Builders of American Communities, September 20, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Publication, Federal Works Agency and the U.S. Housing Authority, vol. 3, no. 1 -- vol. 3, no. 8
  - Housing- General - 1950s (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Housing America's Forgotten Families. A Six Point Program (Box 7, Folder 19)
      National Association of Home Builders.
    - The FHA Story In Summary. 1934-1959, January 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Hard Facts About the Housing Picture, April 11, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Albert M. Cole, Federal Housing and Home Finance Agency
    - Housing Definitions As They Relate to Programs of the Housing and Home Finance Agency, January 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Federal Housing and Home Finance Agency
    - Films Helpful to Housing and Redevelopment Agencies, October 1, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials
    - News Sheet of the International Federation for Housing and Town Planning, February 1, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Publication, vol. 35
    - News Sheet of the International Federation for Housing and Town Planning, October 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Publication, vol. 53
    - Federal Housing Administration Press Release No. 54-92, October 27, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      RE - the Housing Act of 1954; Section 220 and 221-- private lenders and builders
    - Rehabilitation and Neighborhood Conservation Housing Insurance, Administrative Rules and Regulations Under Sections 220 and 221 of the National Housing Act..., October 15, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Federal Housing Administration (attached to press release above)
    - Housing Accomplishments In 1959, December 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Valuation of Sites for Low-Rent Public Housing (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Housing and Home Finance Agency, Urban Renewal Administration
    - Excerpts from Remarks by Commissioner Julian H. Zimmerman, Mortgage Bankers Association, September 24, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Address of Albert M. Cole, U.S. Housing Administrator, At Fourth National Construction Industry Conference, December 11, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - The Block Statistics Program in the 1960 Census of Housing, January 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Department of the Census, U.S. Department of Commerce
    - FHA Home Owner's Guide, November 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Federal Housing Administration (revised edition, earlier edition in 7-18)
    - The Next Twenty Years In Public Housing, April 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Drayton S. Bryant, Social Work (publication)
    - Address by Mr. Stewart Bates, President of Central Mortgage and Housing Corporation to the Annual Convention of the National House Builders' Association, January 14, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - A Summary of the Evolution of Housing Activities In the Federal Government, December 1, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - The Low-Rent Program. 1934-1957., January 1, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - First Report on ACTION's $250,000 Study of Roadblocks to U.S. Housing, October 1, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      House and Home (publication)
    - Housing Preferences of Farm Families in the Northeast, January 2, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      James E. Montgomery, Cornell University
    - U.S. Housing. A New Program. (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Charles Abrams, Tamiment Institute
    - American Home Ownership vs. Public Housing. A Manual of Debate On This Issue. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - How Big Is the Housing Job?, October 1, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Revised Edition, Housing and Home Finance Agency
    - Climate and Architecture. Selected References, March 1, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Twenty Five Year Record of Federal Housing Administration, May 19, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Congress Record (publication) vol. 105, no. 80
    - The Question of Extending Federal Housing Aid. Pro & Con., March 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Congressional Digest (publication) vol. 38, no. 3
    - The War on Substandard Housing. (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Reinhold P. Wolff and David K. Gillogly, University of Miami
  - Housing - U.S.
    - Housing - U.S. - Alabama, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Housing - U.S. - Arizona, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Housing - U.S. - California, 1940-1950 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Housing - U.S. - California, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Housing - U.S. - California-Oakland, 1940-1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Housing - U.S. - Colorado, 1940, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Housing - U.S. - Connecticut, 1940-1950 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Housing - U.S. - Connecticut-Hartford, 1940-1950 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Housing - U.S. - Connecticut-Hartford, 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Housing - U.S. - Connecticut-New Heaven, 1940-1950 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Housing - U.S. - Delaware, 1940-1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Housing - U.S. - Florida, 1940-1950, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Housing - U.S. - Georgia, 1940, 70 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Housing - U.S. - Georgia, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Housing - U.S. - Georgia, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Housing - U.S. - Hawaii, 1940-1950,1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Housing - U.S. - Illinois, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Housing - U.S. - Illinois, 1940-1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Housing - U.S. - Idaho, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Housing - U.S. - Illinois-Chicago, 1930-1940 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Housing - U.S. - Illinois-Chicago, 1940-1950 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Housing - U.S. - Indiana, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Housing - U.S. - Indiana, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Housing - U.S. - New York - Ithaca, 1950-1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Housing - General, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Housing - General, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Housing - General, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Housing - General, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Aged - Indiana, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Aged - Minnesota, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Housing - Aged - Ohio, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Aged - Foreign - Australia, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Construction &Codes General, 1950-1960 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General, 1940-1950 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General - District of Columbia, 1950-1960 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General - Alabama (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes General - Arkansas, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Georgia, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Massachusetts, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Michigan, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Minnesota (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - New York, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Pennsylvania (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes - Puerto Rico, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Housing - Construction & Codes, Foreign - Austria, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Construction Prefab, 1930,1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Construction Prefab, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Defense Workers, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Defense Workers (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Housing - Disabled, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Dictionaries, 1940,1960 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Housing - Education, 1940-1950 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Housing - Finance General, 1930-50 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Housing - Finance General, 1950-60 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Housing - Finance General, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Housing - Finance General, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Finance General, 1930-40 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Employers, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Finance - Cooperative Enterprise - N.Y. - NYC (Oversized), 1955 (Box 70)
  - Housing - Finance Corporate, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Finance Corporate Enterpries, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Housing - Finance Corporate Enterpries, 1920,40 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Housing - Finance Limited Dividend, 1930-40 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Finance - Rents (Oversized), 1952 (Box 69)
  - Housing - Finance Mortgage, 1950-60 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Finance Mortgage, 1950-60 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Housing - Finance Mortgage, 1950-60 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Finances - Mortgages (Oversized), 1959 (Box 69)
  - Housing - Finance Private Enterpries, 1940,70 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Law - U.S - General, 1930-50 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Finance Rents, 1940-60 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Finance Rents, 1930-40,60 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Finance Rents (Oversized), 1952 (Box 69)
  - Housing - Law - U.S - General, 1940-50 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Housing - Law - U.S - General, 1950-70 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Law - Foreign - Canada, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Housing - Law - Foreign - Great Britain (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Housing - Law - Foreign - Netherlands, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. Acts - California (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Housing - Law - U.S - Connecticut, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - Hawaii (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - Illinois (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - New Jersey, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - New York, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - New York, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - Ohio, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - Tennessee, 1930-50 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Law - U.S. - Virginia (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1942,1943 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Housing - U.S. Acts, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Housing - Market Analysis - New York - New York City, 1940,60 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Housing - Market Analysis - New York - New York City, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Housing - Market Analysis - New York - New York City, 1940-1950 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Housing - Market Analysis, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Housing - Public Finance, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Rehabilitation, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Market Analysis, 1910,40 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Market Analysis, 1950-1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Rental, 1950-1960 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Housing - Rental, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Housing - Rental - Foreign, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Rental, 1930-40 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Rental, 1910,1930-50 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Housing - Rental, 1950-1960 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Social Aspects, 1930-1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Social Aspects, 1920-1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - Connecticut (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - Minorities, 1940-1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S - Illinois, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - Maryland, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - New Jersey, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - Ohio, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1930,1950 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - Tennessee, 1940-1950 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - U.S. - Puerto Rico (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - Foreign - Netherlands, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - Discrimination, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - Integration, 1950-1960 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - Integration, 1940-1960 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Housing - Social Aspects - Integration, 1950-1960, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Connecticut, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Connecticut, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Connecticut, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Connecticut, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Connecticut, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - General, 1930-1060 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Florida, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Maryland, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Michigan, 1950-1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Housing - Statistics - U.S. - New York (Oversized), 1942 (Box 69)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Virginia, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Statistics U.S - Washington, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Statistics Canada - Toronto, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Foreign - Hong Kong, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Veterans, 1940-1950 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Statistics - California, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Housing - Foreign - Greece, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Housing - Foreign - Hong Kong, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Housing - Foreign - India, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Housing - Foreign - Israel (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Housing - Foreign - Japan, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Foreign - Latin America, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Housing - Foreign - Netherland, 1950-1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Housing - Foreign - New Zealand, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Foreign - Nigeria, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Housing - Foreign - Norway, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Housing - Foreign - Peru, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Housing - Foreign - Poland, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Foreign - Spain, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Housing - Foreign - Venezuela, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Housing - Foreign - Sweden, 1920-30,1950 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Housing - Foreign - Switzerland, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Housing - Foreign - Singapore (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Foreign - Yugoslavia (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - Rochester, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - Syracuse, 1930-1940 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - Syracuse, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - Yonkers, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - Misc.Cities, 1940-1970 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - Misc.Cities, 1940-1960 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Housing - U.S. - North Carolina, 1930-40,1960-70 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Housing - U.S. - North Carolina - Charlotte, 1940-1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Housing - U.S. - Ohio - Cincinnati, 1940-1970 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Housing - U.S. - Ohio - Misc. Cities, 1950-1960 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Housing - U.S. - Ohio - Misc. Cities, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Housing - U.S. - Ohio - Misc. Cities, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Housing - U.S. - New York - New York City, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 1)